Yakanton Idol
Three.
Yes, sir.
Curtains
Really already
Yes, sir.
I am
I'm a person who never stops talking, aren't I?
Yes, yes.
And I am also the MC of the group.
Oh, you have a role?
Yes, I have a role.
When I talk, I talk.
Yes, that's right.
But even before that, I am a talker,
Yes, yes.
I think I could talk all the time if someone was around,
I can talk all the time.
I have an image of Tohoku-san's backstage area as being a lively place,
Even in that situation.
Yes, that's right.
But everyone at Touhoku-san is quite talkative,
Yes, yes.
Everyone is talkative, but I feel like I can talk to anyone, even if they are not a member of the group.
You must be very suited for this job.
Really?
That's important.
I like talking a lot.
That's why I like radio so much.
I see. So you also do radio work.
I do some radio work in Tohoku,
Someday, I would like to do an All Night Nippon.
Do you listen to the radio?
Yes, they do. The All Night Nippon is with Nogizaka46, for example.
Yes, yes.
Do you talk a lot at home?
Oh, you know, I don't talk at home.
Hey! Really?
You don't talk much at home, where you can really relax?
It's fate.
Uncle Nippon called me.
What?
I went on Instagram to advertise, and then, oh, I hung up.
I lost it. I'll see you later, please.
See you later. This is fate, I'm sure of it.
Are you sure?
It's true. Uncle Nippon.
I'm already over 20 years old, so I can do it in the middle of the night.
This is the producer of the StarProfessional festival.
Really? Please push it.
I can speak for myself.
I'll be fine. Don't worry. I have to say I love it.
Oh, I'm sorry. I'm talking.
Talking? Oh, you mean at home?
I'm sorry.
It turns off at home,
Oh, it turns off there?
That's right. I'm the type of person who turns off when I get home,
So I try to be quiet and not talk at home.
I see. I was wondering if it was the same at home,
I thought it was the same at home, but it was different when I was a student.
I used to talk a lot when I was a student.
In the past, when I was in high school, I used to stay at the lesson hall for about three hours with the members,
What's that?
Or games.
Or we would go to a restaurant after leaving the lesson hall and talk,
That kind of thing still happens often,
We are very close. We don't think so.
We don't think so, but people around us say we get along very well.
Well, I think so.
Really?
There is a sense of unity there, isn't there? The group.
Yes, there is. When we want to accomplish something,
I think we all hate it when we can't do it,
I think there is a part of us that hates to lose,
I think I have a competitive streak, so that part is probably true,
I mean seriously.
So, I think that's why we are trying to overwhelm the other groups in number.
Well, but the momentum is totally different.
Really? I'm glad.
It's a common battle.
Oh, it's a common battle?
Yes, it happens.
I see.
Satomi, the God of Legs Love.
Ms. Satomi, who loves the beauty goddess of legs.
Thank you very much for your support!
Thank you for everything, everyone!